trackitt.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the privacy terms of our Website, www.trackitt.com, as owned and operated by Path2USA.com, Inc. (â€œTrackittâ€) and the Service we provide.

**Your Privacy  
**Trackitt is committed to your privacy and takes it very seriously. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section at the end of our Privacy Policy.

**Information We Collect  
**Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to Trackitt when you use our Website/Service. Visitors to our Website can find our more about our Service. As a Visitor, you are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information. However, if you decide to become a Member of our Website to use our Service, you will provide at least some Personally Identifiable Information to Trackitt in order for us to provide you with our Service. As a Member, we collect your Personally Identifiable Information in the following ways:

**At Registration  
**We collect your username, password, email address, nationality, ZIP code, profession, and employer size at the time of registration.

**Profile Information  
**In your Member Profile, you may provide additional information such as your locale, case file history, and other related information. 

**Online Forms  
**There may be places in our Service where you fill out online forms. The information you enter into these online forms may contain information that you might consider to be personal.  

**Computer Information Collected  
**When you visit most our Website, or any website for that matter, there is certain amount of computer information that is automatically collected by the interaction of your web browser with the website that is typically considered Non Personal Information. Trackitt also collects the following:

**Cookies  
**Our Website uses cookies to identify which areas of our Website/Service you have visited, so the next time you visit, we can better personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to use certain functionality on our Website/Service correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.

**Web Beacons  
**We may also use a technology called, web beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Website/Service and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails and why they opened our emails. Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website. We do not link Non Personal Information from Web Beacons to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission.

**Automatic Information  
**Finally, just by browsing our Website or using our Service, we automatically receive certain types of information such as the URL of the website from which you entered our Website. We also receive the website to which you’re headed when you leave our Website. We also receive the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet service provider name, web browser type, and computer operating system. We use all of this this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website and Service. 

**How We Use Your Information  
**Trackitt uses the information we receive as provided below.

**Website Communications  
**When Trackitt communicates with you about our Website/Service, we may use the email address you provided on your Profile and/or send messages through the messaging features associated with our Service. We may also send you emails/messages to inform you about changes or service messages regarding our Website/Service. Finally, we may also send you emails/messages with promotional information about Trackitt or our newsletter, unless you have opted out of receiving such information. You can change contact preferences at any time using the My Profile link on our Website. While you can opt-out of promotional messages, you cannot opt-out of receiving service messages.

**Customizing Our Content  
**Trackitt may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to customize your experience on our Website/Service.

**Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties  
**Trackitt does not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to Trackitt with regards to our Website/Service (i.e. payment processors, website hosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.  

  **Community Discussion Boards  
**Our Service offers the capability for Members to communicate through online Community Discussion Boards. Trackitt does not generally filter what is posted on such discussion boards. If you chose to post on these discussion boards, please use care when exposing any Personally Identifiable Information as such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose Personally Identifiable Information through postings.

**Promotions and Newsletter Mailing List  
**When you become a Member, we may automatically add you to our promotions and newsletter mailing list. If you no longer wish to be on our mailing list, you can always opt out of further such emails from us. Please remember that such opt-out doesn’t affect emails related to your account (i.e. billing) or general information and updates about our Service and Website.

  **Legally Required Releases of Information  
**Trackitt may have need to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our Terms of Service; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members; and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of Trackitt, our Users, employees, and affiliates.

  **Disclosures to Successors  
**If Trackitt is acquired or merges, in whole or in part, to another entity that would become responsible for providing the Service to you, we would have the right to transfer your Personally Identiable Information to such entity and that entity would have the right to use your Personally Identifiable Information according to the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by such entity. 

**Changing Your Information  
**You may change your Personally Identifiable Information at any time using the Account & Settings Tab on our Website, including removing yourself from our mailing list. If at any time you need assistance, just send us an email or customer service request form with your request. 

**Protecting Your Child’s Privacy  
**We follow the United States’ Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Even though our Service is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18 (child), we realize that a child may attempt to access our Service. We do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from a child; however, you acknowledge that we cannot accurately verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are parent or legal guardian who suspects their child is attempting to use our Service, please contact us immediately to remove your child’s information. We may ask you to provide identification to confirm that you are indeed the child’s parent or legal guardian. If you are under the age of 18, please do not attempt to use our Service unless you have your parent’s permission.  

**Links to Other Websites  
**Our Website will likely contain links to other websites. Trackitt has no control of such websites and you agree that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy. These websites will likely have their own privacy policies. We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience. You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies and other legal documents of these websites to see how they treat your personal information. 

**Our Email Policy  
**Trackitt and our affiliates fully comply with the CAN-SPAM Act as enacted in the United States. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from Trackitt and/or our affiliates. We agree that we will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission.  

**Our Security Policy  
**Trackitt has constructed our Website and Service using industry standard encryption and authentication tools to protect your Personally Identifiable Information. When we collect your Personally Identifiable Information through our Website, we encrypt this information and attempt to prevent unauthorized access to it by using industry standard technologies, such as encryption software, routers and firewalls. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot completely guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information is completely protected. We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Service and not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Service when not in use, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a public computer.

**Payment Sources  
**You may have to provide a payment source (i.e. credit card or PayPal) to use some of the Services on Trackitt. You understand that we use third-party billing providers to process your payment source for providing our Service to you. We work such providers to insure your payment source information is protected, and we will actively protect your payment source information while it’s in our possession. However, you understand and agree that we can’t control nor can we be liable for the acts of third parties. If you see what you believe to be fraudulent transactions regarding our Service, please contact us immediately. We will work with you and authorities as best we can to help resolve such issues.

**Privacy Policy Updates  
**Trackitt reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.  

**Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy  
**If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please contact us by using the Contact Us request form. 

**Definitions**
